<blog>
	<post>
		<date>June 4, 2022</date>
		<author>Sourabh Kulesh</author>
		<title>Firefox Translations Add-on Released by Mozilla Translates Web Pages Offline</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/firefox_translations_mozilla_1654349169566.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Firefox Translations offers support for a total of eight languages.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Firefox Translations add-on by Mozilla has been released. The new tool has been developed under 

			The Bergamot Project which is aimed to provide an option that runs directly on users' machines for web page translation and,

			 at the same time, preserve their privacy. The add-on will translate the text in and from any language by using the user's computer

			  resources and the data will not be sent to the cloud for processing. It is currently available for translation in eight languages,

			   and work is in progress for further four languages.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>June 4, 2022</date>
		<author>Agence France-Presse</author>
		<title>Elon Musk's Twitter Deal Faces Strong Opposition as Advocacy Groups Launch Campaign to Stop Acquisition</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/twitter_main_image_unsplash_1654246094057.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Elon Musk also faces a lawsuit filed by shareholders accusing him of pushing down Twitter's stock price.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Advocacy groups on Friday launched a campaign to stop Elon Musk from buying Twitter as the proposed purchase cleared review by US antitrust authorities.

		Twitter said that the deal for Musk to acquire the company was a step closer to being sealed with the passing of a deadline for it to be challenged under a US antitrust law.

		The Tesla chief's $44 billion (roughly Rs. 3,41,855 crore) deal to take the one-to-many messaging platform private still faces review by other regulators and must be approved 

		by shareholders.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>June 3, 2022</date>
		<author>David Delima</author>
		<title>Apple Patent Reimagines MacBook With Apple Pencil Replacing Function Row</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/macbook_apple_pencil_support_yankodesign_1654263464253.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Apple visualises a Pencil housed above the keyboard that could also be used for input.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Apple has reportedly applied for a revamped patent that would support an Apple Pencil mounted above the MacBook keyboard. 
		
		The claims include the ability to magnetically retain or secure the Pencil when it is placed the storage area and use the pencil 
		
		as function keys while housed in the chassis. The patent, which the company first applied for last year, imagines the Pencil as a replacement 
		
		for the function keys row. There's no word from Apple on plans to incorporate the technology in upcoming MacBook models.</body>
	</post>
</blog>